So this week has not gone to plan well
we went to go get our car washed.
Somehow,
The truck in front of us,
I don't know if their tires were too big
and they slipped or did it got cut in the conveyor belt,
but we ended up colliding with the truck in the car wash.
Look how close we are, Jaemyun!
I feel like there's something wrong.
Yeah.
I feel like they put us in too close,
or the truck didn't do it properly.
Look at this!
Look at that, Jaemyun!
Like it's on, are we on the hook or something?
Let's get out and look at it.
So, we are now in the process of having to get quotes for that to get repainted
and there's a little like dent. It's not a big damage
but it's still it's only
it's a brand new car
so we're gonna get it fixed
so we're dealing with that
and then Rhyden came home from school yesterday
there's some incident after school
i still don't really understand what happened
but it ended up with him getting pushed
He fell, and I don't know if he, from the push
or from how he fell,
it reinjured the collarbone injury he had in Korea.
So we spent all morning at prompt care.
Getting him seen by a doctor.
He didn't go to school today.
He's in a sling.
And so we're being referred to an orthopedic doctor.
And all my classes started,
which are a lot more work than I expected, again.
And I'm going to have to postpone my test,
because there's no way
I'm going to have time to study for it,
on top of everything else, we have going on this month, week.
And now what are you doing?
And now I'm attaching pompoms.
Cause I'm procrastinating.
Oh, because I have to finish my college application.
I have to write those essays,
but I don't know what to talk about.
So that's really what I'm procrastinating is working on that.
What are you working on, honey?
Oh, and just so you know, Taylor Swift's coming out with new music later this week.
Anything to add?
Oh, we also booked our trip to Hawaii.
At least that's done,
but we spent a lot of money on that.
We have family coming in a couple of weeks.
So we have to get ready for that.
My mom did pay for the cleaner to come.
Really?
Yeah.
She's coming two or three days before family gets here to...
I'm just gonna keep rambling if you keep the camera in front of me, Jaemyun.
Can you explain what happened to him in Korea?
Well, I don't really know what happened in Korea,
but it sounded like he tried to explain it to the doctor today
so it was what he was going too fast on the scooter
and fell and hit a curb on his collarbone
right?
so that he got a hairline fracture
and he was using the sling then
but it looked like it was getting better, so he got out of the sling
But the doctors now said it still looks like it's healing,
so that's why they're going to refer us to a different doctor.
He didn't have a new hairline fracture,
but they thought it was strange that
even though it had been so long since he had that injury,
that he still showed...
like that it was still healing
they thought it should have been healed by now
and then i did ask
because that's the same collarbone that as uh
when he was born he also had a fracture
then so i asked if it like
if he just is going to have a weak collarbone
so she was concerned about his diet
and if he maybe has a vitamin deficiency
if he's not healing as he should
and is maybe weak or something
so she recommended to talk to the pediatrician
but I mean he eats.
he eats decently,
so, I mean, he...
No problem with dairy, no problem with vegetables,
no problem with fruit and stuff.
What's the next step?
So I need to figure out through Kia
so we don't like void our warranty and stuff that who actually can fix it.
If we can get it fixed at the Hyundai dealership,
or if I need to take it to the Kia dealership,
and then we'll have to get a quote
and then we have to talk the car wash to get it paid for
just have to figure all that out
Rhyden is having the school
the kindergarten class is having an abc parade
And his letter is the letter P,
so we're decorating it.
Um,
yeah, maybe I went a little too crazy with it,
but... That's okay.
So, what are you putting?
Pompoms, for the letter P.
Well, what else?
We have pencils,
and pipe cleaners
And... That's it, I think.
Pink. Lots of pink and lots of purple.